A Guide to the Newsmap, World News of the Week, A. M. S. Bulletins Collection, 1942-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Newsmap, World News of the Week, A. M. S. Bulletins Collection, 1942-1969
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2015-011
7.0 cu. ft. 5 boxes
The collection consists of several Army and other U. S. military publications, primarily relating to World War II, including: Newsmap, Newsmap Overseas Edition, World News of the Week, and A. M. S. Bulletins. There are additional reports and charts from other agencies. Materials in the collection date from 1942 to 1969.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Alternate Form Available
The University of North Texas Digital Library includes digitized copies of Newsmaps from 1942-1946. These digital copies are available online. For more information and to browse holdings, see the description of the collection.
The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) also includes a series of Newsmaps from 1942. For more information on the publication in general and on NARA's holdings, see the National Archives Catalog record.
Acquisition Information
The Newsmap, World News of the Week, A. M. S. Bulletins Collection was donated to Special Collections prior to 2000.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of several Army and other U. S. military publications including: Newsmap, Newsmap Overseas Edition, World News of the Week, and A. M. S. Bulletins. Holdings for the World News of the Week cover 1944-1949. Holdings for Newsmap cover 1942-1947. Holdings for Newsmap Overseas Edition are from 1943. Holdings for A. M. S. Bulletins cover 1943-1962. Except for the A. M. S. Bulletins, the holdings represent a full run for the time period covered. A. M. S. Bulletins are scattered issues from between 1943 and 1962.
In addition, the collection contains a small group of other related publications from military or government agencies. These include charts, reports, and memoranda from the 1950s and 1960s.
Arrangement
Titles of which the collection has a significant run are in chronological order within each title. The last box (Box 5) contains reports, charts, and items for which we have only one or two items.
Index Terms
Genre and Form Terms:
Maps (documents)
Subjects:
World War II
Contents List
- A.M.S Bulletins, 1943-1969 (Box 5)
  - August 1943, Vol. 1
  - October 1943, Vol. 2
  - November 1943, Vol. 3
  - December 1943, Vol. 4
  - January 1944, Vol. 5
  - March 1944, Vol. 6
  - May 1944, Vol. 7
  - June 1944, Vol. 8
  - July 1944, Vol. 9
  - August 1944, Vol. 10
  - September 1944, Vol. 11
  - October 1944, Vol. 12
  - December 1944, Vol. 13
  - February 1945, Vol. 14
  - March 1945, Vol. 15
  - April 1945, Vol. 16
  - May 1945, Vol. 17
  - July 1945, Vol. 18
  - August 1945, Vol. 19
  - September 1945, Vol. 20
  - October 1945, Vol. 21
  - November 1945, Vol. 22
  - June 1946, Vol. 23
  - October 1946, Vol. 24
  - January 1947, Vol. 25
  - February 1948, Vol. 26
  - March 1948, Vol. 27
  - November 1948, Vol. 28
  - March 1956, Edition 2, Vol. 29
  - February 1951, Vol. 30
  - May 1952, Vol. 31
  - November 1956, Edition 1, Vol. 35
  - August 1959, Edition 1, Vol. 36
  - June 1961, Vol. 37
  - July 1961, Vol. 38
  - September 1962, Vol. 39
  - September 1962, Vol. 40
- Newsmap, 1942-1946 (Box 1-3)
  - Monday, April 27, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 1
  - Monday, May 4, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 2
  - Monday, May 11, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 3
  - Monday, May 18, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 4
  - Monday, May 25, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 5
  - Monday, June 1, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 6
  - Monday, June 8, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 7
  - Monday, June 15, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 8
  - Monday, June 22, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 9
  - Monday, June 29, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 10
  - Monday, July 6, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 11
  - Monday, July 13, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 12
  - Monday, July 20, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 13
  - Monday, July 27, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 14
  - Monday, August 3, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 15
  - Monday, August 10, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 16
  - Monday, August 17, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 17
  - Monday, August 24, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 18
  - Monday, August 31, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 19
  - Monday, September 7, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 20
  - Monday, September 14, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 21
  - Monday, September 21, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 22
  - Monday, September 28, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 23
  - Monday, October 5, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 24
  - Monday, October 12, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 25
  - Monday, October 19, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 26
  - Monday, October 26, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 27
  - Monday, November 2, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 28
  - Monday, November 9, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 29
  - Monday, November 16, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 30
  - Monday, November 23, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 31
  - Monday, November 30, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 32
  - Monday, December 7, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 33
  - Monday, December 14, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 34
  - Monday, December 21, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 35
  - Monday, December 28, 1942, Vol. 1, No. 36
  - Monday, January 14, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 37
  - Monday, January 11, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 38
  - Monday, January 18, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 39
  - Monday, January 25, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 40
  - Monday, February 1, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 41
  - Monday, February 8, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 42
  - Monday, February 15, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 43
  - Monday, February 22, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 44
  - Monday, March 1, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 45
  - Monday, March 8, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 46
  - Monday, March 15, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 47
  - Monday, March 22, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 48
  - Monday, March 29, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 49
  - Monday, April 5, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 50
  - Monday, April 12, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 51
  - Monday, April 19, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 52
  - Monday, April 26, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 1
  - Monday, May 3, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 2
  - Monday, May 10, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 3
  - Monday, May 17, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 4
  - Monday, May 24, 1943, Vol. 1, No. 5
  - Monday, May 31, 1943, Vol. II, No. 6
  - Monday, June 7, 1943, Vol. II, No. 7
  - Monday, June 14, 1943, Vol. II, No. 8
  - Monday, June 21, 1943, Vol. II, No. 9
  - Monday, June 28, 1943, Vol. II, No. 10
  - Monday, July 5, 1943, Vol. II, No. 11
  - Monday, July 12, 1943, Vol. II, No. 12
  - Monday, July 19, 1943, Vol. II, No. 13
  - Monday, July 26, 1943, Vol. II, No. 14
  - Monday, August 2, 1943, Vol. II, No. 15
  - Monday, August 9, 1943, Vol. II, No. 16
  - Monday, August 16, 1943, Vol. II, No. 17
  - Monday, August 23, 1943, Vol. II, No. 18
  - Monday, August 30, 1943, Vol. II, No. 19
  - Monday, August 26, 1943, Vol. II, No. 20
  - Monday, September 13, 1943, Vol. II, No. 21
  - Monday, September 20, 1943, Vol. II, No. 22
  - Monday, September 27, 1943, Vol. II, No. 23
  - Monday, October 4, 1943, Vol. II, No. 24
  - Monday, October 11, 1943, Vol. II, No. 25
  - Monday, October 18, 1943, Vol. II, No. 26
  - Monday, October 25, 1943, Vol. II, No. 27
  - Monday, October 21, 1943, Vol. II, No. 28
  - Monday, November 8, 1943, Vol. II, No. 29
  - Monday, November 15, 1943, Vol. II, No. 30
  - Monday, November 22, 1943, Vol. II, No. 31
  - Monday, November 29, 1943, Vol. II, No. 32
  - Monday, December 6, 1943, Vol. II, No. 33
  - Monday, December 13, 1943, Vol. II, No. 34
  - Monday, December 20, 1943, Vol. II, No. 35
  - Monday, December 27, 1943, Vol. II, No. 36
  - Monday, January 3, 1944, Vol. II, No. 37
  - Monday, January 10, 1944, Vol. II, No. 38
  - Monday, January 17, 1944, Vol. II, No. 39
  - Monday, January 24, 1944, Vol. II, No. 40
  - Monday, January 31, 1944, Vol. II, No. 41F
  - Monday, February 7, 1944, Vol. II, No. 42F
  - Monday, February 14, 1944, Vol. II, No. 43F
  - Monday, February 21, 1944, Vol. II, No. 44F
  - Monday, February 28, 1994, Vol. II, No. 45F
  - Monday, March 6, 1944, Vol. II, No. 46F
  - Monday, March 13, 1944, Vol. II, No. 47F
  - Monday, March 20, 1944, Vol. II, No. 48F
  - Monday, March 27, 1944, Vol. II, No. 49F
  - Monday, April 3, 1944, Vol. II, No. 50F
  - Monday, April 10, 1944, Vol. II, No. 51F
  - Monday, April 17, 1944, Vol. II, No. 52F
  - Monday, April 24, 1944, Vol. III, No. 1F
  - Monday, May 1, 1944, Vol. III, No. 2F
  - Monday, May 8, 1944, Vol. III, No. 3F
  - Monday, May 15, 1944, Vol. III, No. 4F
  - Monday, May 22, 1944, Vol. III, No. 5F
  - Monday, May 29, 1944, Vol. III, No. 6F
  - Monday, June 5, 1944, Vol. III, No. 7F
  - Monday, June 12, 1944, Vol. III, No. 8F
  - Monday, June 19, 1944, Vol. III, No. 9F
  - Monday, June 26, 1944, Vol. III, No. 10F
  - Monday, July 3, 1944, Vol. III, No. 11F
  - Monday, July 10, 1944, Vol. III, No. 12F
  - Monday, July 17, 1944, Vol. III, No. 13F
  - Monday, July 24, 1944, Vol. III, No. 14F
  - Monday, July 31, 1944, Vol. III, No. 15F
  - Monday, August 7, 1944, Vol. III, No. 16F
  - Monday, 14 August, 1944, Vol. III, No. 17F
  - Monday, 21 August, 1944, Vol. III, No. 18F
  - Monday, 28 August, 1944, Vol. III, No. 19F
  - Monday, 4 September, 1944, Vol. III, No. 20F
  - Monday, 11 September, 1944, Vol. III, No. 21F
  - Monday, 18 September, 1944, Vol. III, No. 22F
  - Monday, 25 September, 1944, Vol. III, No. 23F
  - Monday, 2 October, 1944, Vol. III, No. 24F
  - Monday, 9 October, 1944, Vol. III, No. 25F
  - Monday, 16 October, 1944, Vol. III, No. 26F
  - Monday, 23 October, 1944, Vol. III, No. 27F
  - Monday, 30 October, 1944, Vol. III, No. 28F
  - Monday, 6 November, 1944, Vol. III, No. 29F
  - Monday, 13 November, 1944, Vol. III, No. 30F
  - Monday, 20 November, 1944, Vol. III, No. 31F
  - Monday, 27 November, 1944, Vol. III, No. 32F
  - Monday, 4 December, 1944, Vol. III, No. 33F
  - Monday, 11 December, 1944, Vol. III, No. 34F
  - Monday, 18 December, 1944, Vol. III, No. 35F
  - Monday, 25 December, 1944, Vol. III, No. 36F
  - Monday, 1 January, 1945, Vol. III, No. 37F
  - Monday, 8 January, 1945, Vol. III, No. 38F
  - Monday, 15 January, 1945, Vol. III, No. 39F
  - Monday, 22 January, 1945, Vol. III, No. 40F
  - Monday, 29 January, 1945, Vol. III, No. 41F
  - Monday, 5 February, 1945, Vol. III, No. 42F
  - Monday, 12 February, 1945, Vol. III, No. 43F
  - Monday, 19 February, 1945, Vol. III, No. 44F
  - Monday, 26 February, 1945, Vol. III, No. 45F
  - Monday, 5 March, 1945, Vol. III, No. 46F
  - Monday, 12 March, 1945, Vol. III, No. 47F
  - Monday, 19 March, 1945, Vol. III, No. 48F
  - Monday, 26 March, 1945, Vol. III, No. 49F
  - Monday, 2 April, 1945, Vol. III, No. 50F
  - Monday, 9 April, 1945, Vol. III, No. 51F
  - Monday, 16 April, 1945, Vol. III, No. 52F
  - Monday, 23 April, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 1F
  - Monday, 30 April, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 2F
  - Monday, 7 May, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 3F
  - Monday, 14 May, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 4F
  - Monday, 21 May, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 5F
  - Monday, 28 May, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 6F
  - Monday, 4 June, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 7F
  - Monday, 18 (11?) June, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 8F
  - Monday, 18 June, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 9F
  - Monday, 25 June, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 10F
  - Monday, 2 July, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 11F
  - Monday, 9 July, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 12F
  - Monday, 16 July, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 13F
  - Monday, 23 July, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 14F
  - Monday, 30 July 1945, Vol. IV, No. 15F
  - Monday, 6 August, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 16F
  - Monday, 13 August, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 17F
  - Monday, 20 August, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 18F
  - Monday, 27 August, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 19F
  - Monday, 3 September, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 20F
  - Monday, 10 September, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 21F
  - Monday, 17 September, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 22F
  - Monday, 24 September, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 23F
  - Monday, 1 October, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 24F
  - Monday, 8 October, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 25F
  - Monday, 15 October, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 26F
  - Monday, 27 October, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 27F
  - Monday, 29 October, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 28F
  - Monday, 5 November, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 29F
  - Monday, 12 November, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 30F
  - Monday, 19 November, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 31F
  - Monday, 26 November, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 32F
  - Monday, 3 December, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 33F
  - Monday, 10 December, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 34F
  - Monday, 17 December, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 35F
  - Monday, 24 December, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 36F
  - Monday, 31 December, 1945, Vol. IV, No. 37F
  - Monday, 7 January, 1945 (1946?), Vol. IV, No. 38F
  - Monday, 14 January, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 39F
  - Monday, 21 January 1946, Vol. IV, No. 40F
  - Monday, 28 January, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 41F
  - Monday, 4 February, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 42F
  - Monday, 11 February, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 43F
  - Monday, 18 February, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 44F
  - Monday, 25 February, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 45F
  - Monday, 4 March, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 46F
  - Monday, 11 March, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 47F
  - Monday, 18 March, 1946, Vol. IV, No. 48F
  - Vol. IV, No. 49
  - Vol. IV, No. 50
  - Vol. IV, No. 51
  - Vol. IV, No. 52
  - Vol. V, No. 1
  - Vol. V, No. 2
  - Vol. V, No. 3
  - Vol. V, No. 4
- Newsmap Overseas Edition, 1943 (Box 5)
  - Monday July 12, 1943, Vol. II, No. 12
  - Monday, July 19, 1943, Vol. II, No. 13
  - Monday, July 26, 1943, Vol. II, No. 14
  - Monday, August, 2, 1943, Vol. II, No. 15
  - Monday, August 9, 1943, Vol. II, No. 16
  - Monday, August 16, 1943, Vol. II, No. 17
  - Monday, August 23, 1943, Vol. II, No. 18
  - Monday, August 30, 1943, Vol. II, No. 19
  - Monday, September 6, 1943, Vol. II, No. 20
  - Monday, September 13, 1943, Vol. II, No. 21
  - Monday, September 20, 1943, Vol. II, No. 22
  - Monday, September 27, 1943, Vol. II, No. 23
  - Monday, October 4, 1943, Vol. II, No. 24
  - Monday, October 11, 1943, Vol. II, No. 25
  - Monday, October 18, 1943, Vol. II, No. 26
  - Monday, October 25, 1943, Vol. II, No. 27
  - Monday, November 1, 1943, Vol. II, No. 28
  - Monday, November 8, 1943, Vol. II, No. 29
  - Monday, November 15, 1943, Vol. II, No. 30
  - Monday, November 22, 1943, Vol. II, No. 31
  - Monday, November 29, 1943, Vol. II, No. 32
  - Monday, December 6, 1943, Vol. II, No. 33
- World News of the Week, 1944-1949 (Box 3-5)
  - Monday, March 13, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 28
  - Monday, March 20, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 29
  - Monday, March 27, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 30
  - Monday, April 3, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 31
  - Monday, April 10, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 32
  - Monday, April 17, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 33
  - Monday, April 24, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 34
  - Monday, May 1, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 35
  - Monday, May 8, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 36
  - Monday, May 15, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 37
  - Monday, May 22, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 38
  - Monday, May 29, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 39
  - Monday, June 5, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 40
  - Monday, June 12, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 41
  - Monday, June 19, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 42
  - Monday, June 26, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 43
  - Monday, July 3, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 44
  - Monday, July 10, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 45
  - Monday, July 17, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 46
  - Monday, July 24, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 47
  - Monday, July 31, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 48
  - Monday, August 7, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 49
  - Monday, August 21, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 51
  - Monday, August 28, 1944, Vol. 6, No. 52
  - Monday, September 4, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 1
  - Monday, September 11, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 2
  - Monday, September 18, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 3
  - Monday, September 25, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 4
  - Monday, October 2, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 5
  - Monday, October 9, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 6
  - Monday, October 16, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 7
  - Monday, October 23, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 8
  - Monday, August 14, 1994, Vol. 6, No. 50
  - Monday, October 30, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 9
  - Monday, November 6, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 10
  - Monday, November 13, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 11
  - Monday, November 20, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 12
  - Monday, November 27, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 13
  - Monday, December 4, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 14
  - Monday, December 11, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 15
  - Monday, December 18, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 16
  - Monday, December 24, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 17
  - Monday, December 31, 1944, Vol. 7, No. 18
  - Monday, January 8, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 19
  - Monday, January 14, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 20
  - Monday, January 22, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 21
  - Monday, January 29, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 22
  - Monday, February 5, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 23
  - Monday, February 12, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 24
  - Monday, February 19, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 25
  - Monday, February 26, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 26
  - Monday, March 5, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 27
  - Monday, March 12, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 28
  - Monday, March 19, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 29
  - Monday, March 26, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 30
  - Monday, April 2, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 31
  - Monday, April 9, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 32
  - Monday, April 16, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 33
  - Monday, April 23, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 34
  - Monday, April 30, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 35
  - Monday, May 7, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 36
  - Monday, May 21, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 38
  - Monday, May 28, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 39
  - Monday, June 4, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 40
  - Monday, June 11, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 41
  - Monday, June 18, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 42
  - Monday, June 25, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 43
  - Monday, July 2, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 44
  - Monday, July 9, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 45
  - Monday, July 16, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 46
  - Monday, July 23, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 47
  - Monday, July 30, 1948, Vol. 7, No. 48
  - Monday, August 6, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 49
  - Monday, August 13, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 50
  - Monday, August 20. 1945, Vol. 7, No. 51
  - Monday, August 27, 1945, Vol. 7, No. 52
  - Monday, September 3, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 1
  - Monday, September 10, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 2
  - Monday, September 17, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 3
  - Monday, September 24, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 4
  - Monday, October 1 1945, Vol. 8, No. 5
  - Monday, October 8, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 6
  - Monday, October 15, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 7
  - Monday, October 22, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 8
  - Monday, October 29, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 9
  - Monday, November 5, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 10
  - Monday, November 12, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 11
  - Monday, November 19, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 12
  - Monday, November 26, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 13
  - Monday, December 3, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 14
  - Monday, December 10, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 15
  - Monday, December 17, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 16
  - Monday, December 24, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 17
  - Monday, December 31, 1945, Vol. 8, No. 18
  - Monday, January 7, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 19
  - Monday, January 14, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 20
  - Monday, January 21, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 21
  - Monday, January 28, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 22
  - Monday, February 4, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 23
  - Monday, Feb 11, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 24
  - Monday, February 18, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 25
  - Monday, February 25, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 26
  - Monday, March 4, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 27
  - Monday, March 11, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 28
  - Monday, March 18, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 29
  - Monday, March 25, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 30
  - Monday, April 1, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 31
  - Monday, April 8, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 32
  - Monday, April 15, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 33
  - Monday, April 22, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 34
  - Monday, April 29, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 35
  - Monday, May 6, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 36
  - Monday, May 13, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 37
  - Monday, May 20, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 38
  - Monday, May 27, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 39
  - Monday, June 3, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 40
  - Monday, June 10, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 41
  - Monday, June 17, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 42
  - Monday, June 24, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 43
  - Monday, July 1, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 44
  - Monday, July 8, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 45
  - Monday, July 15, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 46
  - Monday, July 22, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 47
  - Monday, July 29, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 48
  - Monday, August 5, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 49
  - Monday, August 12, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 50
  - Monday, August 19, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 51
  - Monday, August 26, 1946, Vol. 8, No. 52
  - Monday, September 2, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 1
  - Monday, September 9, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 2
  - Monday, September 16, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 3
  - Monday, September 23, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 4
  - Monday, September 30, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 5
  - Monday, October 6, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 6
  - Monday, October 14, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 7
  - Monday, October 21, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 8
  - Monday, October 28, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 9
  - Monday, November 4, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 10
  - Monday, November 11, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 11
  - Monday, November 18, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 12
  - Monday, November 25, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 13
  - Monday, December 2, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 14
  - Monday, December 9, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 15
  - Monday, December 16, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 16
  - Monday, December 23, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 17
  - Monday, December 30, 1946, Vol. 9, No. 18
  - Monday, January 6, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 19
  - Monday, January 13, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 20
  - Monday, January 20, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 21
  - Monday, January 27, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 22
  - Monday, February 3, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 23
  - Monday, February 10, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 24
  - Monday, February 17, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 25
  - Monday, February 24, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 26
  - Monday, March 3, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 27
  - Monday, March 10, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 28
  - Monday, March 17, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 29
  - Monday, March 24, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 30
  - Monday, March 31, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 31
  - Monday, April 7, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 32
  - Monday, April 14, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 33
  - Monday, April 21, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 34
  - Monday, April 28, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 35
  - Monday, May, 6, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 36
  - Monday, May 12, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 37
  - Monday, May 19, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 38
  - Monday, May 26, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 39
  - Monday, June 2, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 40
  - Monday, June 9, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 41
  - Monday, June 16, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 42
  - Monday, June 23, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 43
  - Monday, June 30, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 44
  - Monday, July 7, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 45
  - Monday, July 14, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 46
  - Monday, July 21, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 47
  - Monday, July 28, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 48
  - Monday, August 4, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 49
  - Monday, August 11, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 50
  - Monday, August 18, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 51
  - Monday, August 25, 1947, Vol. 9, No. 52
  - Monday, September 1, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 1
  - Monday, September 8, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 2
  - Monday, September 15, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 3
  - Monday, September 22, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 4
  - Monday, September 29, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 5
  - Monday, October 6, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 6
  - Monday, October 13, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 7
  - Monday, October 20, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 8
  - Monday, October 27, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 9
  - Monday, November 3, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 10
  - Monday, November 11, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 11
  - Monday, November 17, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 12
  - Monday, November 24, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 13
  - Monday, December 1, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 14
  - Monday, December 8, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 15
  - Monday, Dec 15, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 16
  - Monday, December 22, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 17
  - Monday, December 29, 1947, Vol. 10, No. 18
  - Monday, January 5, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 19
  - Monday, January 12, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 20
  - Monday, January 19, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 21
  - Monday, January 26, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 22
  - Monday, February 2, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 23
  - Monday, February 9, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 24
  - Monday, February 16, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 25
  - Monday, February 23, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 26
  - Monday, March 1, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 27
  - Monday, March 8, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 28
  - Monday, March 15, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 29
  - Monday, March 22, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 30
  - Monday, March 29, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 31
  - Monday, April 5, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 32
  - Monday, April 12, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 33
  - Monday, April 19, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 34
  - Monday, April 26, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 35
  - Monday, May 3, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 36
  - Monday, May 10, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 37
  - Monday, May 17, 1048, Vol. 10, No. 38
  - Monday, May 24, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 39
  - Monday, May 31, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 40
  - Monday, June 7, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 41
  - Monday, June 14, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 42
  - Monday, June 21, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 43
  - Monday, June 28, 1948, Vol. 10, No. 44
  - Monday, September 6, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 2
  - Monday, September 13, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 3
  - Monday, September 20, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 4
  - Monday, September 27, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 5
  - Monday, October 4, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 6
  - Monday, October 11, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 7
  - Monday, October 18, 1948, Vol. 11, No. 8